¡­That¡¯s said we do plan to ship a device of meego program sometime this year,
¡­and I think it is critical important to deliver that and get the feedback for that,
I have seen the device running
and it is beautiful and elegant,
¡­and the hardware is interesting and the software is powerful
¡­and it has Qt and QML on it and  all the technologies that people were heard about.
We also announce that the third part of our strategy that we  were going to engage in  the work on a new disruptive platform.
We don¡¯t want ever had happened to us, what is happen just recently which is get caught from behind.
¡­and the smart phone had to turn , you know, to another place to build devices.
So as we evaluate the feedback from meego, we¡¯re going to consider that feedback and the technologies were in,
for inclusion our, you know, next generation technologies or platform technologies that we talk about.