No one has ever escaped it
And that is as it should be
because Death is very likely the single best invention of Life
It is Life's change agent
It clears out the old to make way for the new
Right now the new is you
but someday not too long from now
you will gradually become the old and be cleared away
Sorry to be so dramatic
but it is quite true
Your time is limited
so don't waste it living someone else's life
Don't be trapped by dogma
which is living with the results of other people's thinking
Don't let the noise of others' opinions drown out your own inner voice
And most important
have the courage to follow your heart and intuition
They somehow already know what you truly want to become
Everything else is secondary